查莉成长日记上集回顾
Previously on Good luck Charlie...
咱们全家要去夏威夷度假啦
The Duncans are going to Hawaii!
什么
What?!
-我叫泰迪  -你好  泰迪  我叫卡伊
-I'm Teddy. -Aloha, Teddy. I'm kai.
您昨天没有参加分时入住座谈会
We missed you yesterday at the time share presentation.
如果您今天还没有参加
If you don't attend the one today,
我们将强迫让您缴纳这次旅行的全部费用
We'll be forced to charge you for your entire trip.
你搞什么
What are you doing?
对你施诅咒
Putting a curse on you.
游泳遇到了水母
Swimming and jellyfish.
厄运缠身啊
Things keep happening.
老天爷啊  如果你能让我活下去
Please, God, if you let me live through this,
我保证以后会行善积德的
I promise I'll do something good.
查莉  查莉
Charlie? Charlie?
查莉  出来啊
Charlie? Here, girl.
出来啊  在我急哭之前
Come out, come out wherever you are,
快出来啊
Before Teddy starts to cry.
-嘿  宝贝  -噢  老爸啊
-Hey, honey. -Oh, dad.
-出什么事了  -噢  没事
-What's up? -Oh, nothing.
只是对树做一个快速检查
Just a quick plant inspection.
没错  是榕属
Yep, ficus.
泰迪  你没事吧
Teddy, you okay?
我很好
I'm fine.
你看见家里的那个谁  在旅店附近吗
So have you seen anyone around the hotel from the family,
比如  孩子的位置啊  既然您发现了我
You know, kid-wise? You've already seen me,
所以我猜一定看见了别的孩子  比如PJ
So I guess it'd have to be one of the others like P.J.
或者盖比  或者查莉
Or Gabe or Charlie.
你脑袋撞门上了
Did you hit your head again?
你撞了吗
Did you hit yours?
问这么多干嘛
What's with all the questions?
等一下  等一下  给你  宝贝
Hold on, hold on. Here you go, sweetie.
-你需要戴上这个  -为什么
-You need to wear one of these. -Why?
因为这样就不会走失了
Because we don't want you to get lost.
走吧  好了  跟上  这边走
Let's go. Okay, come on, let's go this way.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z  万山绿遍
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第十九集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E19  Sun Show, Part 2
快点  PJ  快给我你的恐惧清单
Come on, P.J. I need your list of fears.
别催我  这倒提醒我了
Don't rush me. That reminds me,
第二十七条  被  “催促”怎么写
Number 27, "being... how do you spell "rushed"?
给我吧
Gimme that.
“PJ的恐惧清单  小丑  恐高  坠落”
"things P.J.'s afraid of... clowns, heights, falling,"
蜘蛛  独角兽
Spiders, unicorns,
“巨魔  妖怪”
"Trolls, ogres."
成了  不如我们先从现实中有的入手
Okay, how about we start the things actually exist?
好主意
Good idea.
在夏威夷的哪里能找到妖怪
Where you gonna find an ogre in Hawaii?
成了  第一条开始
Okay, item number one.
-准备好了吗  -我想应该是好了
-<i>You ready?</i> -<i>Yeah, I think so.</i>
你好  PJ  你还好吧
Hiya, P.J. How you doing?
还好
Fine.
不要害怕
Don't be afraid.
请允许我介绍下自己
Allow me to introduce myself.
我是一个友善的小丑
I'm not scary the clown.
看上去你出汗了
You look a little sweaty.
用我的手帕吧
Try my handkerchief.
很好
Yeah.
快停下  停下
Make it stop. Make it stop!
任务艰巨啊
This is gonna take a while.
还是要谢谢你
Thank you anyway.
哇  亲爱的  怎么搞的
Whoa, honey! What happened?
还记得我跟你讲过的诅咒吗
Remember that curse I was telling you about?
-显灵了  -你在说什么呢
-That's what happened. -What are you talking about?
过来  我把来龙去脉给你讲清楚
Come here. I'll tell you what I'm talking about.
听着  我和查莉在高尔夫球场
Okay, I was on the putting green with Charlie.
当我闯入圣地时  就被诅咒了
When I stepped on sacred ground and got cursed.
我还在圣地上跳舞
Then I danced on sacred ground.
然后全家都被诅咒了
And got the rest of the family cursed.
还是和这个大粗脖子没关系啊
Still not hearing about the giant neck.
继续听  然后我决定游泳放松下
Okay, then I decided to go for a relaxing swim.
但是遇到了水母
With jellyfish.
为了掩盖下伤痕  我就戴上了个花环
To cover the welts, I put on a lei,
却发现我对鸡蛋花过敏
Only to discover that I'm allergic to the plumeria flower.
这就是大粗脖子的由来
That's how I got a giant neck.
等一下  等一下
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
这一切皆源自诅咒
All of this is because of a curse?
是的  一切
Yes, all of it.
我被困在电梯中  泰迪昏迷
Me getting stuck in the elevator, Teddy getting knocked out,
男孩们坐的直升机差点坠毁
The boys almost crashing in a helicopter accident.
还有你买的这件衬衫
You buying that shirt.
什么  你不喜欢这件吗
What? You don't like this?
我把收据弄丢了  退不了了
I lost the receipt. I can't take it back.
诅咒啊
The curse!
亲爱的  别迷信了  这些和诅咒扯不上关系
Honey, come on. There is no such thing as a curse.
这一切纯属巧合
Everything that has happened is just a coincidence.
好了  你知道你需要什么吗
All right, you know what you need?
四十三号的高领毛衣
A size 43 turtleneck?
亲爱的  你所需要的就是放松
Honey, what you need is a nice relaxing day.
去做水疗  让自己放松下
At the spa. Go pamper yourself.
做做按摩  洗洗蒸气浴
Get a massage. Get a steam.
把这些诅咒的事情抛之脑后
Just get all this curse stuff put out of your head.
好吧  也许你说得对
Okay, maybe you're right.
我反应过度了
I'm overreacting.
当然了
Of course you are.
鲍伯  亲爱的  说实话
Bob, honey, be honest with me.
我现在看起来有多惨
How bad do I look?
每次我双眼凝视你时
Every time I look at you.
看到的都是我那美丽的妻子
All I see is my beautiful wife.
噢  嘴真甜
Aw. That's nice.
听着  这个是我在电视上看到的
Okay, I saw this on tv.
如果你能踏过这些木炭
If you can walk across these coals,
任何事物你都无所畏惧
you won't be afraid of anything.
我有点儿怕
I don't know.
别这样  你能行的  这全靠意念
Come on, you can do it. It's all about mind control.
现在清空你心里的杂念
Now take a moment to empty your mind completely.
好了
Done.
-这么快  -我再检查下
-Already? -Let me check.
好了  空了
Yeah, done.
好吧  过来
Okay, come on.
深呼吸  集中注意力
Take a deep breath and focus.
我来找出那个
I'm just gonna go find the guy...
呜
Whoo!
我做到了
I did it.
PJ  木炭还没点着呢
P.J., the coals weren't lit.
还点吗  用火点吗
Lit? Like fire lit?
没错  你应该走过热腾腾的木炭
Yeah, you're supposed to walk across hot coals.
但是会受伤的  你知道我有敏足症
But that would hurt. And you know I suffer from S.F.S.
-敏足症  -敏感足部症
-S.F.S.? -Sensitive foot syndrome.
我没瞎掰  盖比
It's real, Gabe.
你想为什么我从不玩跳房子
Why do you think I never played hopscotch?
打扰一下  女士  您看见
Excuse me, ma'am, have you seen...
噢
Oh!
老妈
Mom?
怎么搞的
What happened?
全身按摩
Full body massage.
恰好按摩油里面有鸡蛋花的成分
Turns out the massage oil had plumeria in it.
医生说我无大碍
Doctor says I'm gonna be fine.
有够惨吗
Is it bad?
不惨  不惨  您看起来一点儿也不
No no, you've never looked more...
-什么  -没什么  就是有点儿臃肿
-What? -That's it. Just more.
听着  老妈  我要和您说点儿事
Listen, mom, there's something that I need to tell you.
-和查莉有关  -怎么了
-It's about Charlie. -Yeah?
她
She's...
在跳草裙舞
Doing the hula.
噢  太萌了
Oh, that's adorable.
前所未有的场景
That's the greatest thing I've ever seen.
嗨  查莉
Hi, Charlie.
这就是人生的机遇
Welcome to the opportunity of a lifetime.
一个赢得在人间天堂分时入住的机会
A chance to own a timeshare of paradise.
在开始之前  邓肯先生
Before we begin, Mr. Duncan,
快速问答
Quick question.
我把收据弄丢了  退不了货了
I lost the receipt. I can't take it back.
和您的衬衫没关系
It's not about your shirt.
邓肯夫人会来吗
Is Mrs. Duncan on her way?
天啊  希望不会来
Man, I hope not.
如果夫妻双方不能出席座谈会
If both spouses aren't at the presentation,
我们将会收取您此次旅行的费用
We're going to have to charge you for your entire trip.
那好  我马上回去把我的夫人请来
Okay, then I will be right back with my lovely wife.
或者请别人
Or somebody else.
帮个小忙
Quick favor.
我需要你装扮成你妈
I need you to pretend to be mom.
老爸  此时搞怪可不是个好时候啊
Dad, really bad time to get super weird.
我刚知道夫妻双方都要
I just found out that my wife has.
出席分时入住座谈会
To be at the timeshare presentation.
很显然  你老妈都浮肿成那样了  没法去了  求你了
Obviously, I can't take mom. Please.
这是紧急情况
This is an emergency.
好吧  好吧  先等我一会儿
All right, fine, just give me a minute.
-嘿  -噢
-Hey. -Oh.
可以去约会了吗
Ready for our date?
事实上  我还要再延误一会儿
Actually, I have one more slight delay.
我要帮我老爸个忙
I have to help my dad with something.
泰迪  我开始怀疑你不想和我一起约会
Teddy, I'm starting to think you don't wanna hang out with me.
没有  没有  我绝对想
No no no. No, I totally do.
一会儿就完事  一小时后咱们沙滩上见
It's not gonna take long. I'll just meet you on the beach in an hour?
-不见不散  -太好了
-I'll be there. -Great.
-可以走了吗  -别催我  这就走
-Really gotta go. -Don't rush me. I'm coming.
哇  你太像你老妈了
Wow, you are gonna be great as your mom.
嘿  我们在这上面干嘛
Hey, what are we doing up here?
克服你的恐高症
You're gonna overcome your fear of heights.
从悬崖上跳进水里
By jumping off this cliff into the water below.
哇  你疯了吗
Whoa! Are you crazy?
大家常常这么跳
People do it all the time.
没错  但那些人是专业人士
Yeah, but those people are professionals.
没有什么好怕的
There's nothing to be afraid of.
他说的没错  PJ  会没事的
<i>He's right, P.J.</i> <i>It's gonna be okay.</i>
跳吧
<i>Just jump.</i>
停  你疯了吗  你想自杀吗
<i>Stop! Are you crazy?</i> <i>Do you wanna get</i> <i>yourself killed?</i>
PJ  清空杂念
P.J., empty your mind.
安静  他好像能听见我们的谈话
<i>Quiet. I think</i> <i>he can hear us.</i>
加油  你能行的
Come on, you can do it.
我可不这么认为  盖比
I don't think so, Gabe.
也许我应该从比较好解决的问题开始
Maybe I should start with something smaller?
PJ  PJ
P.J. P.J.
干吗
Yeah.
你怎么在这里  你应该在下面的
What are you doing here? You're supposed to be down there.
幸运的是那里有一小块平台  看见了吗
Luckily there was a little ledge, see?
还有一些台阶  看
And some steps, see?
你只跳了四英尺吗（1.2米）
So you jumped four feet?
多刺激啊
And what a rush!
耶
Yeah!
在我们开始之前  先让我们熟悉一下对方
Before we begin, let's get to know each other a little.
不如先从邓肯夫妇开始
Why don't we start with the Duncans?
-那好吧  -请你们站起来介绍下自己
-Of course. -Why don't you stand up and introduce yourselves?
-鲍伯  -泰德  艾米
- Bob. - Ted... Amy.
泰德米
Tedamy.
Tedamy?
好一个有趣的名字
That's an interesting name.
嗯  是啊  我父母就这文化水平
Yeah, well, my parents were really messed up.
嗯  鲍伯和泰德米
So, Bob and tedamy,
你们怎么认识的
How'd this happen?
呃
Uh...
他过去给我家除虫
He was my exterminator.
当他来到我的房间时
And he came over to my apartment.
正背着那种大型毒药箱
With that giant tank of poison on his back.
我就知道他是我生命中的鲍哥哥
And I just knew that bobby-boo was the one for me.
你们清楚的  我是不背毒药箱的
Just so you know, I don't wear the tank on my back.
没人会关心细节的
No one cares about the details.
-我关心  -我们用得着在这儿讨论这个吗
- I care. - Do we have to do this here?
让我们认识下一位  好不  该你们了
Let's meet someone else, shall we? You guys.
爽啊  征服恐惧的感觉真好
Man, it feels good to conquer your fears.
P.J.  你没征服任何恐惧
P.J., you didn't conquer anything.
你竟然被我的小丑样子给吓跑了
You ran from a clown,
走过的木炭压根没加热过
Walked across slightly warm coals.
往下跳了四英尺就被岩石接住了
And jumped down four feet onto a ledge.
我事先又不知道那块会突出来
Which I did not know would be there.
P.J.  我已经许诺过要做些善事
P.J., I made a promise that I would do something good.
可是你知道我是对谁许的吗
And do you know who I made that promise to?
上面的家伙
The guy upstairs.
西雅图的比尔
Bill from Seattle?
他貌似是个好人  可是你管他
He seems like a nice guy, but what does he care about...
再上面  我是对上帝许的诺  P.J.
More upstairs. I promised God, P.J.
我们应该再试试
We gotta keep trying.
好
Fine.
嗯  我有床单恐惧症
Well, I have a fear of bedspreads.
嗯  你看  我已经克服了
Oh, look, I overcame it.
其实那是条被子
Actually, that's a quilt.
啊  这是被子
Ooh, this is a quilt?
好吧  既然你不想为自己做点改变
Fine. If you won't do it for yourself,
也不为我  那为了查莉总行吧
Or me, do it for Charlie.
她很仰慕你啊
She looks up to you.
真的
She does?
看到了吧
Did you see that?
好  那我再试一次
Fine. I'll give it one more shot.
没想到洗发水里竟然有鸡蛋花
Turns out there's plumeria in the shampoo.
说实话  看上去糟吗
Be honest, is it bad?
不不  挺好的  老妈
No no, you look fine, mom.
噢  那就好
Oh, that's good.
记住  花钱是次要的
Remember, it's not about spending money.
来天堂度假才是主要的
It's about spending your vacation in paradise.
我真得去趟洗手间
I really need to use the restroom.
我们90分钟后会有休息时间的
We have a break coming up in 90 minutes.
我直说好了
I'm gonna make this simple.
我要去撒尿
I am going to pee now.
撒到哪呢  A  那盆植物里
Is it going to be in A: That plant?
B  垃圾桶里
B: That trashcan?
C  走廊的厕所里
C: The bathroom in the hallway?
请去C处
Please go with c.
行  你可以离开
Fine. You may leave.
现在我们讨论付费计划
Now let's talk about payment plans.
-对不起  -嗯 泰德米
- Excuse me. - Yes, tedamy.
我们在这块儿要待多久
How much longer are we gonna be here?
就5个半多小时
Only five and a half more hours.
不过我跟一个帅哥约好了
But I have a date with a really cute boy.
我听说你已经结婚了
I thought you were married.
是啊  我是结婚了  但还没死
Well, I'm married, not dead.
有什么办法能让我早点离开吗
Is there any way that I can leave sooner?
当然  在纸上签完字
Sure, sign that paper
然后你就可以立马闪人
And you are free to go right now.
太好了  没问题
Great. Okay.
阿罗哈
Aloha.
好  舞会现在正式启动
All right, the ball is now officially rolling.
我只不过去了趟厕所而已
All I did was go to the bathroom.
我们已经卖掉了我们的第一套分时入住房
We have sold our first timeshare unit.
恭喜你们  鲍伯和泰德米邓肯夫妇
Congratulations, Bob and tedamy Duncan.
早知道就挑那盆植物了
Should have picked the plant.
你再说一次这项运动的名字
What did you say this was called again?
滑翔伞  你等会儿会在空中飞起来
Parasailing. You're gonna go up in the air.
-然后会温和的平静的  -在空中飞起来
- And get a gentle peaceful... - Up in the air?
你之前根本没说会在空中飞起来
You didn't say anything about up in the air.
那你说这降落伞干什么用的
What did you think the parachute was for?
降落伞  我还以为是个鲜艳的披风呢
Parachute? I thought this was a very colorful cape.
我怎么弄掉这身装备
How do I get out of this thing?
好好好
Fine fine fine fine.
如果你确定不想滑
If you don't wanna do it,
就这样向船上的那个人示意
just signal the guy on the boat like this.
嘿  船上的人  嘿  船上的人
Hey, boat guy! Hey, boat guy!
那是出发的信号  不是吗
That was the go signal, wasn't it?
是的  看来你要跑起来了
Yep, you might wanna start running.
我好高兴我们直到现在才聚在一起
I'm kind of glad we weren't able to get together until now.
因为这样才算十全十美
Because this could not be more perfect.
我知道  这样才漂亮
I know. It's beautiful.
卡伊  这是我哥哥P.J.
Kai, this is my brother P.J.
P.J.  这是卡伊
P.J., kai.
泰迪  你都干了些什么
Teddy, what did you do?
我本来在海滩上的一个地方正约会
I had a date on the one spot on the beach.
突然一个傻瓜从天而降
Where idiots fall out of the sky.
我是在说分时入住
I'm talking about the timeshare.
房子现在成咱们的了
We now own this room.
我只不过签了一张单子而已
All I did was sign a piece of paper.
那就等于给我们买了套分时入住房
Which bought us a timeshare,
可是我们买不起啊
Which we can't afford.
你是我见过的最烂的妻子
You are the worst wife I've ever had.
好吧  对不起  你怎么不让PJ扮你妻子呢
Well, I'm sorry. Why don't you make P.J. Your wife?
因为我相信他会做的很漂亮
Because I'm sure he'd do a much better job.
大家安静
People. Quiet!
你怎么戴着个拖把
Why are you wearing a mop?
因为我头发都结成团了  想看
Because my hair's coming out in clumps. Wanna see?
不用不用 拖把挺好
No no. Mop's good.
好好盖着它
Mop it up.
嗨  孩子们  有一件事我不得不说
Hey, kids, there's something that I have to tell you.
我知道这听起来很疯狂  但还是要说
I know this is gonna sound really crazy, but here goes.
我们被诅咒了
We've been cursed.
-被诅咒  -是的
- Cursed? - Yes.
夏威夷当地一位暴躁老头干的
By mano, a grumpy hawaiian man.
你要是在圣地上做机器人动作他会不高兴的
Who does not like it when you do the robot on sacred ground.
诅咒  别开玩笑了
A curse? Come on.
想想吧  坏事一件接一件
Think about it. Everything bad
发生 都是在我让大家受到诅咒之后
Started happening after I got us cursed.
-像直升机事故  -还有妈妈突然变胖
- Like the helicopter. - And mom's fatness.
-我的神志不清  -还有妈妈的秃头
- Me getting knocked out. - And mom's baldness.
-分时入住  -还有妈妈的荒谬可笑
- The timeshare. - And mom's grotesqueness.
好了 够了
Okay, got it.
等会  解释一下  分时入住是什么东西
Wait a second. Back up. What's this about a timeshare?
快去跟她解释  鲍哥哥
Go on and tell her, bobby-boo.
-她买的  不是我  -你买了一个分时入住
- She bought it, not me. - You bought a timeshare?
这样的
Okay,
之所以我们会在这个该死的地方
the only reason we were at that stupid thing.
仅仅是因为老爸用不着为这房间付钱
Was so dad wouldn't have to pay for the room.
哇哇哇  我们可别忘了还有诅咒的事
Whoa, but let's not forget about the curse.
好的  你不会要告诉我
Okay, you not telling me about
分时入住跟诅咒没有半点关系吧
a timeshare has nothing to do with a curse.
也许真有
Or does it?
原来如此  那我们会永远被诅咒吗
So that's it. We're cursed forever?
不  我们不会的
No, we are not.
是我让大家这么倒霉透顶的
I got us into this mess,
我会想办法让大家摆脱霉运
and now I'm gonna get us out of it.
我会找到酋长  然后让他解除诅咒
I'm gonna find mano and have him reverse the curse.
什么
What?
我会让酋长解除诅咒
I'll tell mano to reverse the curse.
看来你又得去看医生了  鸡蛋花茶
Looks like you're going to the doctor again. Plumeria tea.
噢  晕
Oh, nuts.
嗨  打扰了  你是酋长吗
Hey, excuse me. Are you mano?
我是酋长
I am mano.
嗯  听着  你给我家人施了诅咒
Yeah, listen, you put this curse on my family.
那请问你能解除它呢
And I was just wondering if you could reverse it.
诅咒
Curse.
-就没有诅咒  -没有
- There is no curse. - There isn't?
我那么说只是为了让游客别踩花草
I just say that to keep the guests out of the plants.
我是位园丁
I'm the gardener.
可发生在我们身上的各种倒霉事又怎么解释
But what about all the bad stuff that's happened to us?
我只能说你们太走运
Just got lucky I guess.
我的家人觉得诅咒是真的
My family thinks the curse is real.
告诉他们不是
Tell them it's not.
我是可以这么做
I could do that.
也许我们可以从中找点乐子
Or we could have a little fun.
你说这话时 眼中散发出邪恶的光芒
You say that with an evil look in your eye.
这让我高兴不已
That gives me pleasure.
诅咒解除仪式现在开始
The curse removal ceremony now begins.
我们能得到他的帮助真走运
We are so lucky he does this.
那还用说
You have no idea.
首先  家人里除了最年轻的男性外
First, the family except for the youngest male,
必须围着母亲单腿跳
Must circle the mother hopping.
同时念咒  又肿又恶心 又肿又恶心
And chanting "Big and gross. Big and gross.
就是那个她  被诅咒最深
She's the one that's cursed the most."
那我应该做什么
What should I do?
这部分最精彩了  你来当机器人
That's the best part. You do the robot.
我做机器人动作很像的
I do a good robot.
又肿又恶心  又肿又恶心
Big and gross, big and gross
就是那个她  被诅咒最深
She's the one that's cursed the most
又肿又恶心  又肿又恶心
Big and gross, big and gross
就是那个她  被诅咒最深
She's the one that's cursed the most...
做的不错啊  同志们  岁月会铭记这一刻的
Looking good, guys. Making memories here.
就是那个她  被诅咒最深
She's the one that's cursed the most...
为什么盖比不用做这个
How come Gabe doesn't have to do this?
不知道  看起来他跟那个酋长相当友好
I don't know. Seems awfully chummy with that mano guy.
同志们  我看他俩是在忽悠咱们
Guys, I think they're just messing with us.
邓肯先生  原来你在这儿
Mr. Duncan, there you are.
我们在处理你的分时入住合约时出了点小差错
We had a little accident with your timeshare contract.
和提基火炬
and tiki torch.
所以如果你不介意的话  我们还需要您妻子的签名
So if you don't mind, we need to get your wife's signature again.
起作用了  别停下
It's working. Keep going!
又肿又恶心  又肿又恶心
Big and gross, big and gross
就是那个她  被诅咒最深
She's the one that's cursed the most.
好  好  好
All right, all right, all right.
我想说句祝酒词  我想说句祝酒词
I wanna make a toast. I wanna make a toast.
给我生命中的至爱
To the love of my life,
我的非常漂亮的老婆艾米
My very beautiful wife Amy.
结婚纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary.
谢谢你让我成为地球上最幸运的男人
Thank you for making me the luckiest man on earth.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you too.
-干杯  -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
哇  很甜蜜吧
Aw, isn't that sweet?
老妈老爸在夏威夷终于享受到他们的最浪漫时刻
Mom and dad finally got to have their romantic moment in Hawaii.
至于我嘛  还有差距
As for me, not so much,
不过没关系  因为家庭度假
But that's okay because family vacations.
最重要的是和家人待在一起
Are about spending time with family.
泰迪  想去散散步吗
Teddy, wanna go for a walk?
嘿  把这包起来
Here, wrap this up.
可你要我...  再见  查莉
What am I supposed... goodbye, Charlie.
明明是好运  查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
随便啦
Whatever.
嗨  我是P.J.邓肯
Hi, I'm P.J. Duncan.
今晚  我们谈论S.F.S的话题谈论得很愉快
Tonight, we've had a lot of fun with the subject of S. F.S...
敏感性脚部综合症
Sensitive foot syndrome.
但是得了敏脚症  后果很严重
But sensitive foot syndrome is a serious problem.
在全球几乎有12个人深受其害
That affects almost a dozen people across the globe.
来  跟着我走
Come, walk with me.
今天脚特别敏感啊
It is a particularly sensitive day.
现在你亲眼见到我和
Now you see what me and
另外11个人有多么痛苦了吧
almost eleven other guys have to go through.
嘿  你在做什么呢
Hey. What're you doing?
我在给人们讲S.F.S
I'm inform people about S.F.S.
P.J. 根本没这回事  这种病就不存在
P.J there's no such thing. It doesn't exist.
真的
Really?
我们还有救
We're gonna live!